<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Bruno</string>

    <string name="title_route_planning">Route Planning</string>
    <string name="title_fitness_records">Fitness Records</string>
    <string name="title_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="ok_button">OK</string>
    <string name="yes_button">YES</string>
    <string name="no_button">NO</string>

    <!--  Onboarding  -->
    <string name="get_started_button">Get Started</string>
    <string name="next_button">Next</string>
    <string name="allow_access_button">Allow Access</string>
    <string name="select_button">Select</string>
    <string name="install_button">Install</string>
    <string name="quit_button">Quit</string>
    <string name="loading_diaglog_text">Loading… Please wait</string>
    <string name="onboarding_welcome">Welcome to Bruno!</string>
    <string name="onboarding_welcome_text">Bruno is a fitness app that augments your walk or run routines with randomly generated routes and music discovery.</string>
    <string name="onboarding_record">Learn More About Yourself</string>
    <string name="onboarding_record_text">Bruno automatically archives your past routines, so you can monitor your progress.</string>
    <string name="onboarding_pick_your_avatar">Pick Your Avatar</string>
    <string name="onboarding_request_location_permission_title">Location Permission</string>
    <string name="onboarding_request_location_permission_hint">Generate routes and track route progress</string>
    <string name="onboarding_request_location_service_title">Location Service</string>
    <string name="onboarding_request_location_service_hint">Generate routes and track route progress</string>
    <string name="onboarding_request_active_internet_title">Active Internet</string>
    <string name="onboarding_request_active_internet_hint">Load map data, generate routes, and stream music</string>
    <string name="onboarding_request_spotify_title">Spotify</string>
    <string name="onboarding_request_spotify_hint">Requires Spotify to be installed</string>
    <string name="onboarding_missing_spotify_installation_title">Spotify Not Installed</string>
    <string name="onboarding_missing_spotify_installation_description">Spotify app not found on the device, please install it from the Play Store.</string>
    <string name="onboarding_missing_internet_text">Bruno requires an active internet connection to proceed. Please wait until your device is connected to an active network before proceeding.</string>
    <string name="onboarding_fallback_playlist_title">Pick a Fallback Playlist</string>
    <string name="onboarding_fallback_playlist_hint">Select a Spotify playlist to use during your route if you lose connection to the Internet. Make sure that this playlist is downloaded on your device.</string>
    <string name="onboarding_fallback_playlist_no_playlist_description">You currently have no Spotify playlists. Add a playlist to your Spotify account and configure your fallback playlist in settings.</string>
    <string name="onboarding_fallback_playlist_fail">Something went wrong, please try again later.</string>
    <string name="onboarding_fallback_playlist_not_premium_user">Unfortunately, Bruno requires Spotify Premium to work.</string>
    <string name="onboarding_all_done">All Done!</string>
    <string name="onboarding_permission_title">Bruno Requirements</string>
    <string name="permission_status_name">Permission name</string>
    <string name="permission_status_description">Explain why permission is needed.</string>

    <!--  Settings  -->
    <string name="settings_user_preferences_title">Your Preferences</string>
    <string name="settings_avatar_title">Avatar</string>
    <string name="settings_avatar_hint">Pick a new avatar</string>
    <string name="settings_fallback_playlist_title">Fallback Playlist</string>
    <string name="settings_fallback_playlist_hint">Spotify playlist used when you lose Internet connection</string>
    <string name="settings_debug_preferences_title">Debug Preferences</string>
    <string name="settings_mock_route_generator_title">Route Generator</string>
    <string name="settings_mock_playlist_generator_title">Playlist Generator</string>
    <string name="settings_mock_music_player_title">Music Player</string>
    <string name="settings_mock_location_service_title">Location Service</string>
    <string name="settings_mock_fitness_record_dao_title">Fitness Record DAO</string>
    <string name="settings_mock_spotify_auth_service_title">Spotify Auth Service</string>
    <string name="settings_mock_spotify_playlist_api_title">Spotify Playlist API</string>
    <string name="save_button">Save</string>
    <string name="about_bruno_title">About Bruno</string>
    <string name="version">Version</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions">Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions_hint">All the stuff you agree with Bruno.</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_hint">How Bruno treats your data.</string>
    <string name="credits">Credits</string>
    <string name="credits_hint">Thanks to everybody that made Bruno possible!</string>

    <string name="route_planning_instruction">Plan your route with Bruno</string>
    <string name="route_planning_walking_mode">Walking</string>
    <string name="route_planning_running_mode">Running</string>
    <string name="route_planning_start">Start</string>
    <string name="route_planning_create_route">Create Route</string>
    <string name="route_planning_duration">Duration (Minutes)</string>
    <string name="route_planning_playlist_error">Error generating playlist, please try again!</string>
    <string name="route_planning_greeting">Good day,</string>
    <string name="run_player_connect_title">Hold on tight</string>
    <string name="run_player_connect_message">Bruno is connecting to the music player</string>
    <string name="run_completion_title">Route Completed</string>
    <string name="run_completion_message">Hooray! You have completed your exercise. You can find details in the Fitness Records tab.</string>
    <string name="player_error">Player Error</string>
    <string name="run_exit_title">Are you exhausted?</string>
    <string name="run_exit_message">Bruno doesn\'t like it when you quit in the middle. He will stop playing your music.</string>
    <string name="route_navigation_stop">EXIT</string>
    <string name="fitness_details_leaderboard">Leaderboard</string>
    <string name="fitness_details_stats">Your Stats</string>
    <string name="fitness_details_playlist">Route Playlist</string>
    <string name="fitness_details_you">You</string>
    <string name="fitness_details_bruno">Bruno</string>
    <string name="fitness_details_crown_description">Running award</string>
    <string name="fitness_details_distance_description">Total distance indicator</string>
    <string name="fitness_details_steps_description">Total steps indicator</string>
    <string name="fitness_details_clock_description">Total time elapsed indicator</string>
    <string name="fitness_details_music_description">Music note</string>
    <string name="view_holder_fallback_playlist_name">Bruno playlist name</string>
    <string name="view_holder_fallback_playlist_tracks">108 tracks</string>
    <string name="view_holder_fitness_record_title">June 15 · 11:30 AM</string>
    <string name="view_holder_fitness_record_distance">1.5 km</string>
    <string name="view_holder_fitness_record_duration">1 hour</string>
    <string name="fallback_fail_title">Something went wrong</string>
    <string name="fallback_fail_description">Bruno is unable to continue the run. You have either not yet set a
        fallback playlist or Bruno encountered a problem. Your current progress will be lost.</string>

    <!--  Credits  -->
    <string name="credits_text">
        "Core developers:
    - Boris Chan
    - George Lim
    - Jackie Xu
    - James Huang
    - Mohit Patel
    - Sherry Li

Bruno Icon:
    Evelyn Gondosiswanto

Action Icons:
    Font Awesome

Avatar Arts:
    Icon made by Freepik from www.flaticon.com"
    </string>

    <!--  Privacy Policy  -->
    <string name="privacy_policy_text">
    Privacy policy\n\nThis privacy policy ("Policy") describes how the personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") you may provide in the "Bruno" mobile application ("Mobile Application" or "Service") and any of its related products and services (collectively, "Services") is collected, protected and used. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your Personal Information and how you can access and update this information. This Policy is a legally binding agreement between you ("User", "you" or "your") and this Mobile Application developer ("Operator", "we", "us" or "our"). By accessing and using the Mobile Application and Services, you acknowledge that you have read, understood, and agree to be bound by the terms of this Agreement. This Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that we do not own or control, or to individuals that we do not employ or manage.\n\nAutomatic collection of information\n\nOur top priority is customer data security and, as such, we exercise the no logs policy. We may process only minimal user data, only as much as it is absolutely necessary to maintain the Mobile Application and Services. Information collected automatically is used only to identify potential cases of abuse and establish statistical information regarding the usage of the Mobile Application and Services. This statistical information is not otherwise aggregated in such a way that would identify any particular user of the system.\n\nCollection of personal information\n\nYou can access and use the Mobile Application and Services without telling us who you are or revealing any information by which someone could identify you as a specific, identifiable individual. If, however, you wish to use some of the features in the Mobile Application, you may be asked to provide certain Personal Information (for example, your name and e-mail address). We receive and store any information you knowingly provide to us when you fill any online forms in the Mobile Application. When required, this information may include the following:\n\n- Geolocation data such as latitude and longitude.\n- Certain features on the mobile device such as contacts, calendar, gallery, etc.\n\nYou can choose not to provide us with your Personal Information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of some of the features in the Mobile Application. Users who are uncertain about what information is mandatory are welcome to contact us.\n\nUse and processing of collected information\n\nIn order to make the Mobile Application and Services available to you, or to meet a legal obligation, we need to collect and use certain Personal Information. If you do not provide the information that we request, we may not be able to provide you with the requested products or services. Some of the information we collect is directly from you via the Mobile Application and Services. However, we may also collect Personal Information about you from other sources. Any of the information we collect from you may be used for the following purposes:\n\n- Create and manage user accounts\n- Improve user experience\n- Enforce terms and conditions and policies\n- Protect from abuse and malicious users\n- Respond to legal requests and prevent harm\n- Run and operate the Mobile Application and Services\n\nProcessing your Personal Information depends on how you interact with the Mobile Application and Services, where you are located in the world and if one of the following applies: (i) you have given your consent for one or more specific purposes; this, however, does not apply, whenever the processing of Personal Information is subject to California Consumer Privacy Act or European data protection law; (ii) provision of information is necessary for the performance of an agreement with you and/or for any pre-contractual obligations thereof; (iii) processing is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which you are subject; (iv) processing is related to a task that is carried out in the public interest or in the exercise of official authority vested in us; (v) processing is necessary for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by us or by a third party.\n\nNote that under some legislations we may be allowed to process information until you object to such processing (by opting out), without having to rely on consent or any other of the following legal bases below. In any case, we will be happy to clarify the specific legal basis that applies to the processing, and in particular whether the provision of Personal Information is a statutory or contractual requirement, or a requirement necessary to enter into a contract.\n\nDisclosure of information\n\nDepending on the requested Services or as necessary to complete any transaction or provide any service you have requested, we may share your information with your consent with our trusted third parties that work with us, any other affiliates and subsidiaries we rely upon to assist in the operation of the Mobile Application and Services available to you. We do not share Personal Information with unaffiliated third parties. These service providers are not authorized to use or disclose your information except as necessary to perform services on our behalf or comply with legal requirements. We may share your Personal Information for these purposes only with third parties whose privacy policies are consistent with ours or who agree to abide by our policies with respect to Personal Information. These third parties are given Personal Information they need only in order to perform their designated functions, and we do not authorize them to use or disclose Personal Information for their own marketing or other purposes.\n\nRetention of information\n\nWe will retain and use your Personal Information for the period necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law. We may use any aggregated data derived from or incorporating your Personal Information after you update or delete it, but not in a manner that would identify you personally. Once the retention period expires, Personal Information shall be deleted. Therefore, the right to access, the right to erasure, the right to rectification and the right to data portability cannot be enforced after the expiration of the retention period.\n\nTransfer of information\n\nDepending on your location, data transfers may involve transferring and storing your information in a country other than your own. You are entitled to learn about the legal basis of information transfers to a country outside the European Union or to any international organization governed by public international law or set up by two or more countries, such as the UN, and about the security measures taken by us to safeguard your information. If any such transfer takes place, you can find out more by checking the relevant sections of this Policy or inquire with us using the information provided in the contact section.\n\nThe rights of users\n\nYou may exercise certain rights regarding your information processed by us. In particular, you have the right to do the following: (i) you have the right to withdraw consent where you have previously given your consent to the processing of your information; (ii) you have the right to object to the processing of your information if the processing is carried out on a legal basis other than consent; (iii) you have the right to learn if information is being processed by us, obtain disclosure regarding certain aspects of the processing and obtain a copy of the information undergoing processing; (iv) you have the right to verify the accuracy of your information and ask for it to be updated or corrected; (v) you have the right, under certain circumstances, to restrict the processing of your information, in which case, we will not process your information for any purpose other than storing it; (vi) you have the right, under certain circumstances, to obtain the erasure of your Personal Information from us; (vii) you have the right to receive your information in a structured, commonly used and machine readable format and, if technically feasible, to have it transmitted to another controller without any hindrance. This provision is applicable provided that your information is processed by automated means and that the processing is based on your consent, on a contract which you are part of or on pre-contractual obligations thereof.\n\nThe right to object to processing\n\nWhere Personal Information is processed for the public interest, in the exercise of an official authority vested in us or for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by us, you may object to such processing by providing a ground related to your particular situation to justify the objection.\n\nData protection rights under GDPR\n\nIf you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), you have certain data protection rights and the Operator aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Information. If you wish to be informed what Personal Information we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us. In certain circumstances, you have the following data protection rights:\n\n- You have the right to request access to your Personal Information that we store and have the ability to access your Personal Information.\n- You have the right to request that we correct any Personal Information you believe is inaccurate. You also have the right to request us to complete the Personal Information you believe is incomplete.\n- You have the right to request the erase your Personal Information under certain conditions of this Policy.\n- You have the right to object to our processing of your Personal Information.\n- You have the right to seek restrictions on the processing of your Personal Information. When you restrict the processing of your Personal Information, we may store it but will not process it further.\n- You have the right to be provided with a copy of the information we have on you in a structured, machine-readable and commonly used format.\n- You also have the right to withdraw your consent at any time where the Operator relied on your consent to process your Personal Information.\n\nYou have the right to complain to a Data Protection Authority about our collection and use of your Personal Information. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority in the European Economic Area (EEA).\n\nCalifornia privacy rights\n\nIn addition to the rights as explained in this Policy, California residents who provide Personal Information (as defined in the statute) to obtain products or services for personal, family, or household use are entitled to request and obtain from us, once a calendar year, information about the Personal Information we shared, if any, with other businesses for marketing uses. If applicable, this information would include the categories of Personal Information and the names and addresses of those businesses with which we shared such personal information for the immediately prior calendar year (e.g., requests made in the current year will receive information about the prior year). To obtain this information please contact us.\n\nHow to exercise these rights\n\nAny requests to exercise your rights can be directed to the Operator through the contact details provided in this document. Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests. Your request must provide sufficient information that allows us to verify that you are the person you are claiming to be or that you are the authorized representative of such person. You must include sufficient details to allow us to properly understand the request and respond to it. We cannot respond to your request or provide you with Personal Information unless we first verify your identity or authority to make such a request and confirm that the Personal Information relates to you.\n\nPrivacy of children\n\nWe do not knowingly collect any Personal Information from children under the age of 18. If you are under the age of 18, please do not submit any Personal Information through the Mobile Application and Services. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children\'s Internet usage and to help enforce this Policy by instructing their children never to provide Personal Information through the Mobile Application and Services without their permission. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 18 has provided Personal Information to us through the Mobile Application and Services, please contact us. You must also be at least 16 years of age to consent to the processing of your Personal Information in your country (in some countries we may allow your parent or guardian to do so on your behalf).\n\nLinks to other resources\n\nThe Mobile Application and Services contain links to other resources that are not owned or controlled by us. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other resources or third parties. We encourage you to be aware when you leave the Mobile Application and Services and to read the privacy statements of each and every resource that may collect Personal Information.\n\nInformation security\n\nWe secure information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. We maintain reasonable administrative, technical, and physical safeguards in an effort to protect against unauthorized access, use, modification, and disclosure of Personal Information in its control and custody. However, no data transmission over the Internet or wireless network can be guaranteed. Therefore, while we strive to protect your Personal Information, you acknowledge that (i) there are security and privacy limitations of the Internet which are beyond our control; (ii) the security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and the Mobile Application and Services cannot be guaranteed; and (iii) any such information and data may be viewed or tampered with in transit by a third party, despite best efforts.\n\nData breach\n\nIn the event we become aware that the security of the Mobile Application and Services has been compromised or users Personal Information has been disclosed to unrelated third parties as a result of external activity, including, but not limited to, security attacks or fraud, we reserve the right to take reasonably appropriate measures, including, but not limited to, investigation and reporting, as well as notification to and cooperation with law enforcement authorities. In the event of a data breach, we will make reasonable efforts to notify affected individuals if we believe that there is a reasonable risk of harm to the user as a result of the breach or if notice is otherwise required by law. When we do, we will post a notice in the Mobile Application.\n\nChanges and amendments\n\nWe reserve the right to modify this Policy or its terms relating to the Mobile Application and Services from time to time in our discretion and will notify you of any material changes to the way in which we treat Personal Information. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We may also provide notice to you in other ways in our discretion, such as through contact information you have provided. Any updated version of this Policy will be effective immediately upon the posting of the revised Policy unless otherwise specified. Your continued use of the Mobile Application and Services after the effective date of the revised Policy (or such other act specified at that time) will constitute your consent to those changes. However, we will not, without your consent, use your Personal Information in a manner materially different than what was stated at the time your Personal Information was collected. Policy was created with https://www.WebsitePolicies.com\n\nAcceptance of this policy\n\nYou acknowledge that you have read this Policy and agree to all its terms and conditions. By accessing and using the Mobile Application and Services you agree to be bound by this Policy. If you do not agree to abide by the terms of this Policy, you are not authorized to access or use the Mobile Application and Services.\n\nContacting us\n\nIf you have any questions about this Policy, please contact us.\n\nThis document was last updated on August 3, 2020
    </string>

    <!--  Terms and Conditions  -->
    <string name="terms_and_condition_text">
    Terms and conditions\n\nThese terms and conditions ("Agreement") sets forth the general terms and conditions of your use of the "Bruno" mobile application ("Mobile Application" or "Service") and any of its related products and services (collectively, "Services"). This Agreement is legally binding between you ("User", "you" or "your") and this Mobile Application developer ("Operator", "we", "us" or "our"). By accessing and using the Mobile Application and Services, you acknowledge that you have read, understood, and agree to be bound by the terms of this Agreement. If you are entering into this Agreement on behalf of a business or other legal entity, you represent that you have the authority to bind such entity to this Agreement, in which case the terms "User", "you" or "your" shall refer to such entity. If you do not have such authority, or if you do not agree with the terms of this Agreement, you must not accept this Agreement and may not access and use the Mobile Application and Services. You acknowledge that this Agreement is a contract between you and the Operator, even though it is electronic and is not physically signed by you, and it governs your use of the Mobile Application and Services.\n\nLinks to other resources\n\nAlthough the Mobile Application and Services may link to other resources (such as websites, mobile applications, etc.), we are not, directly or indirectly, implying any approval, association, sponsorship, endorsement, or affiliation with any linked resource, unless specifically stated herein. We are not responsible for examining or evaluating, and we do not warrant the offerings of, any businesses or individuals or the content of their resources. We do not assume any responsibility or liability for the actions, products, services, and content of any other third parties. You should carefully review the legal statements and other conditions of use of any resource which you access through a link in the Mobile Application and Services. Your linking to any other off-site resources is at your own risk.\n\nProhibited uses\n\nIn addition to other terms as set forth in the Agreement, you are prohibited from using the Mobile Application and Services or Content: (a) for any unlawful purpose; (b) to solicit others to perform or participate in any unlawful acts; © to violate any international, federal, provincial or state regulations, rules, laws, or local ordinances; (d) to infringe upon or violate our intellectual property rights or the intellectual property rights of others; (e) to harass, abuse, insult, harm, defame, slander, disparage, intimidate, or discriminate based on gender, sexual orientation, religion, ethnicity, race, age, national origin, or disability; (f) to submit false or misleading information; (g) to upload or transmit viruses or any other type of malicious code that will or may be used in any way that will affect the functionality or operation of the Mobile Application and Services, third party products and services, or the Internet; (h) to spam, phish, pharm, pretext, spider, crawl, or scrape; (i) for any obscene or immoral purpose; or (j) to interfere with or circumvent the security features of the Mobile Application and Services, third party products and services, or the Internet. We reserve the right to terminate your use of the Mobile Application and Services for violating any of the prohibited uses.\n\nIntellectual property rights\n\n"Intellectual Property Rights" means all present and future rights conferred by statute, common law or equity in or in relation to any copyright and related rights, trademarks, designs, patents, inventions, goodwill and the right to sue for passing off, rights to inventions, rights to use, and all other intellectual property rights, in each case whether registered or unregistered and including all applications and rights to apply for and be granted, rights to claim priority from, such rights and all similar or equivalent rights or forms of protection and any other results of intellectual activity which subsist or will subsist now or in the future in any part of the world. This Agreement does not transfer to you any intellectual property owned by the Operator or third parties, and all rights, titles, and interests in and to such property will remain (as between the parties) solely with the Operator. All trademarks, service marks, graphics and logos used in connection with the Mobile Application and Services, are trademarks or registered trademarks of the Operator or its licensors. Other trademarks, service marks, graphics and logos used in connection with the Mobile Application and Services may be the trademarks of other third parties. Your use of the Mobile Application and Services grants you no right or license to reproduce or otherwise use any of the Operator or third party trademarks.\n\nLimitation of liability\n\nTo the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, in no event will the Operator, its affiliates, directors, officers, employees, agents, suppliers or licensors be liable to any person for any indirect, incidental, special, punitive, cover or consequential damages (including, without limitation, damages for lost profits, revenue, sales, goodwill, use of content, impact on business, business interruption, loss of anticipated savings, loss of business opportunity) however caused, under any theory of liability, including, without limitation, contract, tort, warranty, breach of statutory duty, negligence or otherwise, even if the liable party has been advised as to the possibility of such damages or could have foreseen such damages. To the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, the aggregate liability of the Operator and its affiliates, officers, employees, agents, suppliers and licensors relating to the services will be limited to an amount greater of one dollar or any amounts actually paid in cash by you to the Operator for the prior one month period prior to the first event or occurrence giving rise to such liability. The limitations and exclusions also apply if this remedy does not fully compensate you for any losses or fails of its essential purpose.\n\nSeverability\n\nAll rights and restrictions contained in this Agreement may be exercised and shall be applicable and binding only to the extent that they do not violate any applicable laws and are intended to be limited to the extent necessary so that they will not render this Agreement illegal, invalid or unenforceable. If any provision or portion of any provision of this Agreement shall be held to be illegal, invalid or unenforceable by a court of competent jurisdiction, it is the intention of the parties that the remaining provisions or portions thereof shall constitute their agreement with respect to the subject matter hereof, and all such remaining provisions or portions thereof shall remain in full force and effect.\n\nDispute resolution\n\nThe formation, interpretation, and performance of this Agreement and any disputes arising out of it shall be governed by the substantive and procedural laws of Ontario, Canada without regard to its rules on conflicts or choice of law and, to the extent applicable, the laws of Canada. The exclusive jurisdiction and venue for actions related to the subject matter hereof shall be the courts located in Ontario, Canada, and you hereby submit to the personal jurisdiction of such courts. You hereby waive any right to a jury trial in any proceeding arising out of or related to this Agreement. The United Nations Convention on Contracts for the International Sale of Goods does not apply to this Agreement.\n\nChanges and amendments\n\nWe reserve the right to modify this Agreement or its terms relating to the Mobile Application and Services at any time, effective upon posting of an updated version of this Agreement in the Mobile Application. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. Continued use of the Mobile Application and Services after any such changes shall constitute your consent to such changes. Policy was created with https://www.WebsitePolicies.com\n\nAcceptance of these terms\n\nYou acknowledge that you have read this Agreement and agree to all its terms and conditions. By accessing and using the Mobile Application and Services you agree to be bound by this Agreement. If you do not agree to abide by the terms of this Agreement, you are not authorized to access or use the Mobile Application and Services.\n\nContacting us\n\nIf you have any questions about this Agreement, please contact us.\n\nThis document was last updated on August 3, 2020
    </string>
</resources>